What are you looking at?
A poster for that WWI movie I'm in.
Check it out.
Wow! It looks really violent!
I know. I'm coming soon
to a theater near you.
I'm in THX.
I'm unsuitable for children!
-I cannot wait to see this.
-It's generating Oscar buzz.
-I started that!
-I thought I did!
I just talked to my agent..
and the premiere is next week
and you're all invited!
-Will we take a limo?
-Sure!
I love taking limos
when nobody died.
Well, I won't be able to come.
For those who haven't checked
their calendars, today's my due date.
You should come.
Maybe you'll have the baby in the limo.
That way for the first few moments of her
life, she'll think we're really fancy.
I want to thank you guys
for how great you've been during this.
I couldn't have done it without you.
I loved these last 9 months.
I'm looking forward
to the next part..
I am really gonna miss
being pregnant.
That's right. Still no baby.
What's the matter? Is the puffy,
sweaty pregnant lady..
disturbing your precious
coffee time?
Come on, people, make some room.
Sweetie, maybe you'd be
more comfortable here.
You.
Like you haven't done enough.
I know you're miserable.
I wish there was something I could do.
I wish I were a sea horse.
Because with sea horses, it's the male.
They carry the babies.
And then also,
I'd be far away in the sea.
God.
I have never been so uncomfortable
in my entire life.
I know. I remember toward the end..
That's a great story. Tell it while
you're getting me some iced tea.
Oh, God, get out!
Get out, get out, get out!
Let's.
Hey, did you have the baby yet?
Do you want me to sit on you?
Because I'll do it.
-What are you doing here?
-They sent me home from work.
They said, "Start your maternity
leave now. Just rest."
You know what? Screw them!
If they don't want me there,
I'll hang out with you guys.
Or you could do volunteer work.
-Hello?
-Joey, it's Estelle.
I was able to get you and one guest
tickets to your premiere.
-You told me I could have six tickets.
-I sold four on eBay.
You'll be sitting next to HotGuy 372.
So that's it? I only get
to bring one guest?
Yeah. What time you
wanna pick me up?
Hello?
You hear that?
I only get one extra ticket to my premiere.
So somehow I have to pick
between you three and Ross.
-What about me?
-You said you didn't want to go.
I don't. But I would
still like to be acknowledged.
-Because I'm pregnant, I'm invisible?
-Definitely not invisible.
Ross didn't care enough
to be here, so he's out.
-You snooze, you lose.
-He's not snoozing. He's teaching.
Well, then somebody's snoozing.
And, Joey, not that this should affect
you at all, but if you pick me..
I was planning on wearing
a sequin dress cut down to here.
-I haven't seen this dress.
-Star in a movie.
Pick whoever you want. Listen
to your heart. What does it tell you?
Phoebe. Phoebe. Phoebe.
Well..
I think I want to take Chandler.
Phoebe, Phoebe, Phoebe.
-You want to take me?
-Yeah, I wish I could take everybody.
But Chandler's always
supported my career.
He's paid for acting classes,
headshots and stuff.
This will be my way
of paying you back.
So you're never actually
going to pay me back?
Just because he paid for your headshots,
you're gonna take him?
I don't think you're comprehending
just how slutty this dress is.
It's not just the stuff he paid for.
It's everything, you know?
He read lines with me. He went with me
on auditions when I was nervous.
Then he consoled me
after I didn't get parts that I wanted.
You always believed in me, man,
even when I didn't.
I always knew you were gonna make it.
I'm so proud of you.
Thanks, that means a lot to me.
Mon, maybe one of these guys
wants to wear your dress.
-I'm gonna go shave.
-Yeah, well, I'm gonna go spit.
I have to pee.
If I don't come out, it's because I've
choked to death on the potpourri stink.
You hold her nose, I'll blow in her
mouth and the kid'll just.. out of her.
She's a week late.
She's got to have it today.
I don't know. I think
it's still gonna be a while.
Care to make it interesting?
-I bet you she'll have it tomorrow.
-You're on.
-Okay, how much?
-One hundred thousand dollars.
-How about 50 bucks?
-I'll call Zurich and move some money.
All right, whose turn is it
to help me get up?
No one's here.
Oh, damn it!
This is exciting. So glamorous! People
taking our picture. How do I look?
-A little tall.
-What?
Would you crouch down a bit
so that I look taller?
There you go.
It's just so glamorous.
Oh, hey, Mon? Rach is here.
And you're still pregnant.
I'm sorry. I know
how uncomfortable you are.
You know what? You look great.
Yeah, like 50 bucks.
I have to go pee. Apparently this baby
thinks my bladder is a squeeze toy.
Damn it. Here's your 50 bucks.
That's interesting that you lost.
Now, I forget, do you like to lose?
All right, stop it.
-Double or nothing she has it tomorrow.
-Fine.
Until then, General Grant, why don't
you set up camp.. right there?
-Rachel here? We have an appointment.
-In the bathroom.
-Rach, we gotta go.
-In a minute!
People ask why we're not together.
I just don't know what to tell them.
All right, let's go.
Oh, wait a minute.
Do I have to pee again?
No, I'm good.
Do you want to go change first?
The doctor's staying open late for us,
but if you hurry..
-No, I'm fine.
-You don't think that's inappropriate?
-What?
-Good God, man. Don't anger it.
Ross, it is 100 degrees outside.
For the first time in weeks, I am..
Fine. Whatever you want.
You're the mommy.
No! Don't call me "Mommy."
It's bad enough you call
your own mother that.
I'm actually with her on this one.
Come on, Ross.
We're gonna be late.
Either of you want to be Ross?
I thought I knew who the enemy was,
but it was you.
Okay, this is it. This is
my big fight scene coming up.
I'm fighting for every man
in the 82nd Ground Division.
Ross?
Can I ask you something?
When Carol was pregnant with Ben..
were you this irritating?
-Excuse me?
-Nothing. You're just..
You've been a little short with me
lately. I'm not trying to irritate you.
Well, then, you must have
a natural talent for it.
The doctor will be in soon.
Why don't we not speak until then?
Okay.
Seriously. Breathe louder, Ross.
That's great.
We should ask the doctor
if she even knows..
how to deliver a baby
that's half human, half pure evil!
-Hi, Dr. Long. How are you?
-You're nice to her.
She has the drugs.
We'll do a quick check.
Eight days late, huh?
You must be getting uncomfortable.
Yeah, just a tad.
You're 80% effaced. You're on your way.
It still could last a while.
-There are ways to help things along.
-Do them!
Actually, they're things
that you can do. Home remedies.
In my experience, I've found
some are very effective.
-Well, we are ready to try anything.
-There's an herbal tea you can drink.
You can take some castor oil.
There's spicy foods.
We will do all of those.
-Taking a long walk.
-Good. Done.
And there's the one that's
proved most effective: sex.
You've got to be kidding me!
Good job, Joe! Well done! Top-notch!
-You liked it? You really liked it?
-Oh, yeah!
-Well, which part exactly?
-The whole thing! Here we go!
No, no, no. Give me some specifics.
I loved the specifics.
The specifics were the best part.
Hey, what about the scene with
the kangaroo? Did you like that part?
I was surprised to see a kangaroo
in a World War I epic.
You fell asleep!
There was no kangaroo! They didn't
take any of my suggestions!
-I can't believe you fell asleep.
-I can't believe it either.
Maybe it didn't happen.
Maybe you fell asleep
and dreamt the whole thing.
And this conversation we're having
right now is part of that dream.
Wake up, Joe!
-Thanks for coming. See you later.
-Don't go. I'm so sorry.
Look, this guy fell asleep!
He fell asleep too! Be mad at him!
Or call an ambulance!
What did the doctor say?
Any news on when the baby will come?
No. She gave us ideas
on how to induce labor.
We tried them all.
We went for a walk, we tried tea,
castor oil, spicy food. Nothing worked.
There is one thing we didn't try.
But someone thinks that
that will open up a can of worms.
If it's gonna help
bring the baby here, today..
I think you should do it.
-It's sex.
-Do it!
-Monica.
-It's been a really long time for you.
I mean, women have needs.
Do it. Get yours.
Oh, I don't know about that.
I think if the two of you had sex, the
repercussions would be catastrophic.
All right, let's be practical.
If Ross isn't willing, he's not
the only guy you can have sex with.
You could borrow Chandler.
Chandler is good.
Okay, okay. Yeah,
I don't think I wanna do that.
You sure? I'm just saying..
the baby's head
isn't getting any smaller.
Monica, what is the matter with you?
-I just want the baby to be born today.
-Why today?
Okay, fine.
I bet Phoebe that you're gonna have
the baby, and I don't want to lose.
What? While she's been going through
this hell, you've been making money?
You're betting on your friend
staying in this misery?
-I'll take that bet.
-What?
I'm miserable. I may as well
make some money out of it.
Can I get some of that action?
I'm betting against all of you?
I really feel like
tomorrow it's gonna happen.
Okay.
Sixty, 80, 100.
And 50.
And two.
Yeah, baby.
Hey, Sleeping Beauty.
Where have you been?
I want to talk to you. I still feel bad.
Oh, no. Were you upset?
Did you lose sleep?
I'm so sorry.
The reason I came over is to settle things
between us. You've done a lot for me.
I wanted to pay you back
with the premiere, but you missed it.
-So how much do I owe you?
-What?
-I don't want to owe you anything.
-You don't owe me.
-I don't want your..
-We're doing this!
You got me my first headshots.
How much?
-I don't know, $500.
-Okay, $500. What else?
Then there was the second set.
The infamous "booger" headshots.
Okay, so that's another $500.
That's 500 and 500. That's..
-You want a calculator?
-Please.
Here.
All right, what else?
Well, there's acting classes,
stage-combat classes, tap classes..
Which we're still keeping
under our hats.
That dialect coach who helped you
with a Southern accent.
Which, after 20 hours of lessons,
still came out Jamaican.
What the hell are you talking about?
The South will rise again, man.
Yes, money well-spent.
Okay, what else? Rent.
Two, three years of rent,
utilities, food..
Okay, so I'm writing you
a check for..
So you fell asleep during my movie.
Big deal, right?
How do you clear this thing?
Finish your enchilada.
Ross, we've tried all the spicy food.
It's not working.
Okay, here, have one of these peppers.
Oh, God. So hot. Oh, my God.
By the way, you don't want to touch
the pepper and then touch your eye.
I am feeling nothing.
Speaking of hot,
watching you do that..
really makes me want
to have sex with you.
-Stop it.
-Come on! Why are we wasting time?
We know it's gonna work.
It's doctor-recommended.
I'm sorry. But we have to have
some boundaries. My God, I'm dying.
We've done it before.
We'll do it again.
It'll be a nice way
to bookend the pregnancy.
I'm not gonna make love to you
so you'll go into labor.
Make love? What are you, a girl?
Always a great way to get
into a man's pants.
You'll be performing a service.
Think of me as a ketchup bottle.
Sometimes, you have to bang on
the end of it to get it to come out.
I love when you talk dirty to me.
I know it. You're right.
That's not sexy.
Oh, I seem to have dropped my fork.
Let me just bend over and get it.
Oh, God!
Okay, enough.
This is not going to happen.
Come on, Ross. I'm miserable here.
Come on, you started this,
now you finish it!
Come on, wuss. Make love to me.
-You know what?
-What?
Forget it.
What now, Ross,
you're not gonna talk?
How on earth will you ever annoy me?
Oh, wait a minute, I know.
You'd think the jalapeno would
clear up your sinuses, but no!
That's not enough..
What are you doing?
I'm getting that baby out of you!
-Oh, God!
-I know.
Oh, no, no, no.
I think my water just broke.
I am good!
Okay, I got the pillow.
I got the bag.
-You got the keys?
-I got the keys.
We're having a baby.
I didn't have time to read this part
of the books, but do we have time..?
-Not so much.
-Okay, let's go.
-200.
-Thank you.
That's it. I don't care when
the baby comes. No more betting.
Okay.
Hello?
I guess we could bet
one more time.
-Is Rachel having the baby?
-How did you know that?
-Joey! Chandler!
-They're at the coffee house.
You know everything!
Wait. I bet you the baby
is over 7 pounds.
I bet you it has hair!
I bet you it's a girl.
-We know it's a girl.
-I'll give you really good odds.